[{"answer": "I think we need to recognize that we're living longer as Americans -- as people in the world.", "docId": "130211pmt", "aSentId": 45, "question": "Should there be a criteria -- you know, should we elect a politician who's 89?", "qSentId": 44}, {"answer": "Well, I think it goes to performance.", "docId": "130211pmt", "aSentId": 58, "question": "So do we have to stop being less politically correct and just call it as we see it?", "qSentId": 57}, {"answer": "Yes, I think so.", "docId": "130211pmt", "aSentId": 65, "question": "Yes or no?", "qSentId": 64}, {"answer": "But we also get to select.", "docId": "130211pmt", "aSentId": 110, "question": "I think this is about (INAUDIBLE), right?", "qSentId": 109}, {"answer": "When they can't drive.", "docId": "130211pmt", "aSentId": 143, "question": "When do we take somebody's driver's license away?", "qSentId": 142}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130211pmt", "aSentId": 178, "question": "Is it OK to call people out for being overweight?", "qSentId": 177}, {"answer": "The people eating more Big Macs isn't necessarily driving us to --", "docId": "130211pmt", "aSentId": 220, "question": "No, but you're asking, is it OK?", "qSentId": 219}, {"answer": "Well, the --", "docId": "130211pmt", "aSentId": 241, "question": "Why don't you do it?", "qSentId": 240}, {"answer": "Well, we're getting into dangerous stuff when we start giving away secrets and things like that, but I think what it goes to is these guys aren't treated well when they come home.", "docId": "130211pmt", "aSentId": 354, "question": "First of all, do you have any promise whatsoever that this SEAL came out and told this story?", "qSentId": 353}, {"answer": "I got to be honest with you, I think Stan nailed this one.", "docId": "130211pmt", "aSentId": 376, "question": "So, can we blame somebody who is brought up in this generation -- can we expect anybody anywhere in any capacity to keep anything private anymore?", "qSentId": 375}, {"answer": "ALE: This man doesn't get a pension.", "docId": "130211pmt", "aSentId": 393, "question": "He's going to get nothing from it?", "qSentId": 392}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130211pmt", "aSentId": 490, "question": "Does a woman in the public eye have an obligation to make a statement to her fans, to young women who follower, say this is not okay?", "qSentId": 489}, {"answer": "Oh yeah, but that's the problem -", "docId": "130211pmt", "aSentId": 527, "question": "Did you see, he was the only one not standing for Ocean when he got his award?", "qSentId": 526}, {"answer": "Chris brown.", "docId": "130211pmt", "aSentId": 534, "question": "So, we have a problem with Rihanna, what she's doing, and not with what Bobby Brown did?", "qSentId": 533}, {"answer": "Yes, not anything.", "docId": "130211pmt", "aSentId": 562, "question": "How much have you heard about Demi Moore lately?", "qSentId": 561}, {"answer": "I don't think she's having a great time.", "docId": "130211pmt", "aSentId": 589, "question": "What's the problem?", "qSentId": 588}, {"answer": "When I was watching the Grammys last night, I was looking around at the guys saying who is her next target, because that's just how you view her.", "docId": "130211pmt", "aSentId": 607, "question": "I mean, Lindsay Lohan, would we be talking about her if not for her hijinx?", "qSentId": 606}, {"answer": "But she does -- when you say that, it makes her sound like a man eater.", "docId": "130211pmt", "aSentId": 610, "question": "Am I wrong?", "qSentId": 609}, {"answer": "She's like 23.", "docId": "130211pmt", "aSentId": 629, "question": "How old is she?", "qSentId": 628}, {"answer": "No, when I was a kid, my parents wouldn't even let us have water guns.", "docId": "130211pmt", "aSentId": 653, "question": "Are we not getting it, nipping it in the bud?", "qSentId": 652}, {"answer": "I don't even know about that.", "docId": "130211pmt", "aSentId": 682, "question": "I feel like we're probably, if I had to guess, not going to end up getting background checks done, right?", "qSentId": 681}, {"answer": "In large part their job -- we talked about the hero before that killed Osama bin Laden.", "docId": "130211pmt", "aSentId": 702, "question": "Military people are people's heroes because they hold guns?", "qSentId": 701}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "130211pmt", "aSentId": 715, "question": "Do they even matter anymore?", "qSentId": 714}, {"answer": "Well, there's a big stigma on mental health, first of all.", "docId": "130211pmt", "aSentId": 754, "question": "You can't -- but what can we do more now, Stan, across the board, early on, to start to detect some of the mental problems in this country, the mental -- horrible health situation in the country so we don't get to this point?", "qSentId": 753}, {"answer": "Oh my God, I'm investing in that company.", "docId": "130211pmt", "aSentId": 772, "question": "If they had a technology now that early on could test children for various mental disorders, would you say that's invasive or OK to do?", "qSentId": 771}, {"answer": "All right guys, we got to take a break here.", "docId": "130211pmt", "aSentId": 785, "question": "When are we going to start talking about the awesome?", "qSentId": 784}, {"answer": "Of course, they can get it back.", "docId": "130211pmt", "aSentId": 807, "question": "Are these people just wasting their time?", "qSentId": 806}, {"answer": "For the most part, but I think Joe Paterno is different than like a Casey Anthony because Joe Paterno has so much good will to stand on.", "docId": "130211pmt", "aSentId": 815, "question": "Yeah, once people make their decision, if anything, Abby, doesn't it backfire on them because now you look at them and go, they're just cashing in?", "qSentId": 814}, {"answer": "That's what Gary was talking about.", "docId": "130211pmt", "aSentId": 846, "question": "Or am I just being naive?", "qSentId": 845}, {"answer": "I just went on one.", "docId": "130211pmt", "aSentId": 883, "question": "Doesn't he look like a cruise guy?", "qSentId": 882}, {"answer": "Three times.", "docId": "130211pmt", "aSentId": 920, "question": "ALIE: Have you ever been on a cruise?", "qSentId": 919}, {"answer": "Not Samsung.", "docId": "130211pmt", "aSentId": 937, "question": "Has Samsung now taken the lead?", "qSentId": 936}, {"answer": "No, it's fine.", "docId": "130211pmt", "aSentId": 966, "question": "Guys, does everybody have a problem when you're out to dinner and everybody's going like this?", "qSentId": 965}]